freegaysex.com 2008-11-01

# Free Gay Sex - Privay Policy

At Free Gay Sex .com (“FGS”) we strive to help our customers protect their privacy while using our services and visiting our sites.  To protect your privacy, FGS has instituted a number of policies that give you information and control.  FGS: 

  * Provides a link to this privacy statement on all pages that ask for personal information. 
  * Will not store or release personal identifying information about you without first obtaining consent. 
  * Will not knowingly collect or use personal identifying information from children younger than 13. 

This privacy statement discloses our practices for the gathering and use of information from visitors to our own FGS Web sites from people who register for services that we offer online, at our sites and from visitors to third party sites where we are collecting information pursuant to our customer contract.

## Other Sites

This privacy policy applies only to FGS and its Web sites.   Users of our sites should be aware that through links they could be directed to other sites that we do not control.   For example, if you click on a banner advertisement, a sponsored link or on a search result or ranked site, the click takes you off the FGS site and sends you to a site controlled and operated by a third party.   These sites may send you cookies, collect your personal information or provide offensive content.   FGS has no control over the privacy policies or practices of these other sites, and FGS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web sites to which we link, list, rank or identify by means of a search.  FGS has no responsibility for the products, services, policies or actions of third parties or the content of third party Web sites.  In addition, FGS will not censor or edit the content of sites on the World Wide Web.  We encourage you to be aware when you are leaving our sites and to read the privacy policies of each Web site you visit. 

##  Your Acceptance

By using our sites, you signify your agreement to the privacy policies described above.  If you do not agree with our privacy policies, please do not use our sites or products/services.   If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages or we will e-mail you at our discretion.

##  Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our online practices, or your dealings with our Web sites, you can contact:

UIA International Inc  
145-157 St John Street  
2nd Floor  
London  
UK  
EC1V 4PY  
UK  

## **What Type of Personal Information Do We Collect and Use?**

### **Membership services**

If you decide to sign up to our site or to subscribe to our newsletters, our registration form require contact information such as your name, e-mail address and billing address.  We also ask for information related to your Web site such as the name, description and of the site.  In addition, certain Web site services are offered by co-branded (“powered by”) Web pages or sites, which may follow different privacy practices.

### **Listings**

Our online partner and advertiser applications require information such as company name, telephone number, e-mail address, mailing address and a primary and secondary contact within the company.   If you do decide to apply for our partnership or advertiser program, our sales team will contact you after receiving the online application to further explain the partnership or advertiser program.  We also provides an area for individuals seeking employment with our company.   Our human resource department answers all résumé's emailed to us.  We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive.   Such addresses are not used for any other purposes and are not shared with outside parties.  In addition, you may also submit your resume or contact information on a page offered by a co-branded (“powered by”) Web site, which may follow different privacy practices.    

## How Do You Use Personal Information?

Registration information submitted on one of FGS's own sites is used by that site for the purpose for which it was submitted and may also be used by FGS's other sites in order to make your visits to our own sites more easy and enjoyable.  
Personal information may be used in several ways: 

  * To enable us to respond to you or to process, validate and verify service requests and to perform the requested services. 
  * To allow us to charge and invoice you and to contact you regarding changes to the subscribed services. 
  * To provide advertisers with aggregate – never individual – information about our registrants and aggregate usage patterns. 
  * To give our own Web site designers information that's useful for developing new features and services that meet registrants' needs. 
  * To allow us to potentially vary the advertising that registrants see based on their volunteered preferences. 
  * To tailor the registrant's experience on our sties, showing them content we think might interest them or altering the content according to their preferences. 

Except for any other purpose that may be stated expressly in this Privacy Policy, FGS will not use your personal information. Information submitted to us at freegaysex.com as part of online applications for employment or for partner candidates is used by us to evaluate your qualifications for the positions sought.  
We do not merge, associate or link any registration information you submit to us at our sites with any of the navigational or interest information we gather anonymously on our sites.   
In case you change your mind about personal information you have given us or if some of it has changed, we will endeavor to provide a way to review, correct, update or remove personal information you have given us.  
If you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site(s), you can submit your friend's e-mail address.  We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit our site.  We will use your friend's e-mail for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.   The friend may also contact us at  to request that we delete the information.

## Chat Rooms and Forums

Our sites may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users.  Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information to people you do not know.  If you disclose your e-mail address in a chat room or forum, you may receive unsolicited e-mails or “spam”.  We cannot safeguard the privacy of any such information you choose to disclose online in this manner and you must do so carefully and at your own risk.

## If You Contact Us

We do use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive at any of our sites, but such e-mail addresses are not stored or used for any other purpose.

## What Kind of Information Do We Share With Others?

Except as may be stated expressly in this Privacy Policy, FGS does not share personal information with third parties.

## Legal Disclosures

There are a limited number of situations where we may disclose your personal information to others without first receiving your consent:   (1) when legally ordered to do so by a lawful subpoena or court order, (2) if you violate or breach an agreement with us, (3) if we believe conduct by you will harm the property or rights of FGS or those of our affiliate program members, (4) under exigent circumstances to protect the physical safety of FGS, its employees, users or the general public, (5) in connection with the sale of all or substantially all of our company's assets or the sale of an entire Web site or business division or (6) in order to validate credit card numbers for charging for fee services.

## Aggregate Information 

FGS may share aggregate statistical information gathered from the registration process with advertisers, business partners, sponsor or other third parties, but none of them receive individual identifying information about you collected at our sties.  For example, we may tell an advertiser that Z number of visitors visited a certain area on a Web site or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out registration forms, but we would not disclose anything that would identify those individuals.   We share this information only on an aggregate, anonymous basis and never on an individual basis.  

## Anonymous Info

### Our Cookies

Your browser offers so-called “cookies”, which – if you allow their use – store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites.  Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best.  And when you re-visit our sties, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences.  However, cookies tell us nothing about you personally unless you specifically give us additional information.  
We may use cookies to:

  * Keep count of your return visits to our site or our clients' sites. 
  * Accumulate and report anonymous, aggregate, statistical information on Web site usage. 
  * Deliver content specific to your interests. 
  * Save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites. 

We do not use cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information.  Our cookies in and of themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information about you.  We do not merge or associate our cookie information with any personally identifiable information obtained by us or from third parties.  
You also have choices with respect to cookies.  By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies.    However, note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at our sites and on other sites throughout the World Wide Web may not be complete.   Some sites require cookies to function, such as those with e-commerce features.  In addition, if you do not allow cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by us or other Internet sites.

### Third Party Cookies At Our Site

Some of the banner ads displayed on our sites are provide by outside companies.  These ads may contain cookies.  The use of advertising cookies sent by third party servers is standard in the Internet industry.   While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are placed by our advertisers.   We do not have access to these cookies or any information that they may contain; please contact the advertisers for more information on these cookies

### IP Addresses

An IP address is a number assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web.  IP addresses are not personally identifiable information and we have never had the ability to determine your IP address.  Internet Service Providers (ISPs) usually randomly assign IP addresses at the time of dial-up.   For other local area network (LAN) or cable modem users, the ISP or network may permanently assign a specific IP address to a particular computer or other device connected to that network.   Anytime you connect to a site on the Internet, the computers communicating with each other exchange IP addresses.  IP addresses can reveal things like what part of the world you're connecting from, or which Internet Service Provider you are using, but they do not reveal who you are. 

## Web Beacons

Our Web pages and the Web pages of our counter customers or members of our affiliate program contain electronic images (called a “single-pixel gif” or “Web beacon”) that allow us to count page views or to access our counter cookies.  In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a Web page, including an ad banner, can act as a Web beacon.  Web beacons are typically very small, banner like files, but their presence can be easily seen within Internet Explorer by clicking on “View” and then on “Source”.   Web beacons are so small in order not to use valuable space on the computer screen that is better used to display helpful content.  We also include Web beacons in HTML- formatted newsletters containing graphics that we send to opt-in subscribers in order to count how many newsletters have been read.   In addition, some advertising networks that serve ads on our Web sites may use Web beacons within in their clearly visible banner advertisements.  Our Web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personal information about our Web site visitors, they are just the technique we use to compile our anonymous, aggregated statistics about Web site usage.

## **Computer Profiles**

Through our technology, we also collect and accumulate other anonymous data that helps us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors.  For example, we accumulate visitor data relating to referring domains, the type of browsers used, operating system software (e.g. Windows 95 vs. 98), screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement.  We also record number of visits, paths, taken and time spent on sites and pages.  None of this information is personally identifiable and we only share this information in the aggregate, reflecting overall Web site or Internet usage trends.

## **Security**

Our sites have physical, electronic and managerial security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  We take many measures to protect this information while it is stored, including:

  * We use Secure Socket layer (SSL) connections with 128- bit encryption for certain transactions and confidential data.  When you use a secure browser, all information you submit to us is transmitted to us over the Internet in an encrypted form. 
  * We monitor system and application activity logs to identify any unusual activity, from authorized and/or unauthorized individuals accessing our systems and/or making changes to stored information, for investigation.   We regularly perform preventative system maintenance and monitoring to ensure the security of our data systems. 
  * Our servers are maintained in secured access, locked facilities.  NOC attendants monitors our data center 24 hours per day, seven days per week.   Backup tapes are retrieved daily and stored.  All our employees sign confidentiality agreements and only our employees who need information to perform their job and who have passed background checks are granted access to personally identifiable information or any other confidential data. 

You do not need to set up a user ID and password to use our Web sites because we do not require you to establish your identity when you visit our sites. However, if you have subscribed to some of our services you will have to provide passwords.  We recommend you do not divulge your password to anyone.  FGS will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited telephone call or e-mail.  You are responsible for the secrecy of your passwords.  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.   As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.  Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.  You can report network abuse and any risk of security violations to us by e-mail at the above address.

## **Children**

Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Act of 1998 (COPA).   COPA and its accompanying FTC regulation established United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet.  FGS does not knowingly collect contact or personal information from children under 13.   Our sites are not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we have designed our sites to block our knowing acceptance of information from children under 13 wherever age related information is requested.  
It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13.   If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers.   If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under 13, please do so by e-mailing us.

## **E-mails**

We do not ordinarily maintain e-mails that have been sent to us after they have been replied to, but if you would like to review, edit or delete any information previously e-mailed to us that we might still have, send an e-mail to us at the above address.    It's important that you include a copy of the previous e-mail, including its original address line, to enable us to locate it.

## **Unsolicited E-mails _Received by You_**

FGS does not send unsolicited e-mails to non-public addresses or to anyone who has requested we do not contact them.   Any newsletters that we send are only sent to those who have taken affirmative steps to subscribe for them at one of our Web sites.   To stop receiving e-mails or newsletters from FGS, either click on an unsubscribe link on the e-mail or newsletter itself or send a request to be unsubscribed our email address above. FGS also does not condone Spam by our affiliates.  Spam by our hosted customers is prohibited by our Acceptable Use Policy which all affiliates accept on registration.  Our Acceptable Use Policy states, among other things, “Do not e-mail or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, “junk mail”, “Spam”, “chain letters”, “pyramid schemes”, or any other form of solicitation”.   Further, according to our published policy, If FGS becomes aware that a customer is in violation of the law or this Acceptable Use Policy, FGS reserves the right to impose disciplinary action in its sole discretion.  Our disciplinary action may include: removal from our servers of files that violate our Acceptable Use Policy, the expulsion of the customer from FGS Web sites, termination of FGS services, and forfeiture of all commissions.  

## **Cookies**

If you opt out of cookies, your Web site experience at our sites will not be impaired.  You may, however, be required to enter your user or account information and passwords each time they are requested.  You have several options with respect to cookies:

  * By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. 
  * For instructions on how to do this, go to [microsoft.com](http://www.microsoft.com/), [netscape.com](http://www.netscape.com/), etc. 

To remove cookies you may have previously received from us or other Web sites, follow the instructions at [microsoft.com](http://www.microsoft.com/), [mozilla.org](http://www.mozilla.org/), etc.
